

Contact

- **Phone Number** (+54) 9 11 2255 0255
- ➤ Email andres_alejandro_rodriguez @ hotmail.com
- Located in
 Ciudad Autónoma de
 Buenos Aires, Argentina



Proficent in

React/NextJS

Javascript ES6

CSS/SASS

Typescript

Git/Github

NodeJS/Express

Languages

- · Spanish: Native
- · English: Profesional (B2)

Soft Skills

- · Fast learning
- · Organized
- · Task planning
- · Problem solving
- · Perpetual student · Effi
- · Efficient

Andrés Molina

Frontend Developer

Developer with 3+ years of experience in website design and development using mainly React and NextJS. Strong problem-solving skills and a passion for staying up-to-date with the latest industry trends and technologies. Committed to delivering high-quality projects within deadlines while maintaining a strong focus on efficiency and code quality.

Education

O 2020 - 2022

Universidad de Buenos Aires - FADU

Diseño Industrial

2018 - 2019
Escuela de Arte Multimedial Da Vinci

Diseño Multimedial

Work Experience

0 2023

Touch (freelance)

Frontend Developer, Designer

0 2021 - 2023

Aiwa Electronics

Frontend Developer

O 2018 - 2019 Totalhome S.A.

Graphic Designer

Courses

FreeCodeCamp

- Responsive Web Design (300hs)

Coderhouse

- React.js (8 weeks)
- Backend with Node/Express (16 weeks)

▼ Projects

O 2023

Touch - Website (NextJS, Vercel + Framer motion)

Simple institutional website using NextJS with some implementations such as Framer Motion for animations and Swiper for sliders.

2022

Aiwa Electronics - Website (NextJS)

Website for an electronic products company, which dynamically generates product pages, and includes a custom 360° product viewer.



